#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/alec-arehart (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python

Flask

SQL

### Certifications

ITIL Foundation

TDWI Data Science Bootcamp

# Alec Arehart

Senior SecDevOps Engineer at Corning Inc

Washington DC-Baltimore Area

## Summary

Experienced software engineer with a history of working in the machinery and manufacturing industry. Skilled in Back End Development, IoT Systems, and Data Analysis using Python, Java, Go and other programming languages. Graduated with a Bachelor of Science in Business Administration with a focus in Management Information Systems from Shippensburg University of Pennsylvania. Currently pursuing a Master of Information Technology from Virginia Tech.

## Experience

Corning Incorporated
Senior SecDevOps Engineer
August 2022 - Present (9 months)

JLG Industries
Senior Principal Engineer - Software
April 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 5 months)

Leidos Software Developer May 2020 - April 2021 (1 year)

JLG Industries
5 years 5 months
Senior Business Intelligence Analyst
August 2019 - May 2020 (10 months)

Business Intelligence Analyst November 2017 - May 2020 (2 years 7 months) Hagerstown, Maryland

Associate Business Analyst January 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 11 months) Hagerstown, Maryland

JLG Industries
Business Intelligence Intern
May 2014 - August 2014 (4 months)

Quality Bicycle Products
Outbound PPLR
May 2013 - August 2013 (4 months)

## Education

Virginia Tech

Master of Information Technology (MIT), Software Engineering and Big Data · (2018)

Shippensburg University of Pennsylvania
Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.), Management Information
Systems, General · (2010 - 2014)